This is not financial advice.
So I want to be very careful about how I tell you guys.
A lot of you missed out on Bitcoin, okay?
That's the past. You could have got in.
Your friend could have told you.
Blah, blah, blah. Right?
Well, enhanced games just went live on the New York Stock Exchange.
They're currently priced at four dollars and ninety five cents.
This is a whole new generation of sports.
These athletes are enhanced,
legally and professionally monitored.
And they're performing in swimming,
track, strongman and lifting.
The first ever games will be this weekend in Las Vegas,
Nevada. And it's invite only,
so you can't even buy a ticket to it.
It's exclusive.
This is backed by billionaires in the tech industry.
Do you catch my drift? It's currently on the stock market under E N H A.
And it's only been live for about 15 days.
So do with that what you will.
E N H A. You could buy it on Robin Hood. Maybe.
I don't know. This isn't financial advice.